JUSTINE CARR

UX / UI & GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Summary

My strengths are found in creative, critical and liminal thinking and empathy for the human experience. My curious nature allows for understanding, shaping and reframing of assumptions; taking what is learnt and what is habit and pushing for better more intuitive user focused outcomes.

Work Experience

Graphic Designer
MLEI Consulting Engineers
Oct 2018 - Present, Adelaide, South Australia

Role - Rebranding company identity, redesign communications, website audit and responsive website redesign.

Business Owner - Silver smithing Resinate

Mar 2011 - Sep 2018, Adelaide, South Australia

Role - Silver smithing - prototyping and designing of handmade jewellery, marketing and promotion of product - selling B to B and B to C, maintaining online store and social media account.

Graphic Designer Martins Brand House Sept 2004 - May 2007, Adelaide, South Australia

Role - Part of the graphic design team working with national clients and Government Agencies. Brand identities, print communications, annual reports, signage and exhibition fit outs.

Graphic Designer London Borough of Islington Mar 2003 - Jul 2004, London, United Kingdom

Role - In house designer producing communications for the council -booklets, brochures and posters.

Graphic Designer

O'Connor Design Consultants May 2002 - Dec 2002, London, United Kingdom

Role - Print and packaging design for a variety of national clients.

Graphic Designer Ecto Design Jul 2000 - Mar 2002

Role - Small graphics team servicing national and local clients for the land development and real estate industries.

Contact

justinecarr.com.au 0405 326 645 justinemaree@mac.com linkedin.com/in/justine-carr-529664191/

Education

UX UI BOOT CAMP

University of Adelaide Sept 2020 - March 2021

E-CHALLENGE

University of Adelaide Aug 2019 - Nov 2019

BACHELOR OF VISUAL COMMUNICATIONS, GRAPHIC DESIGN

University of South Australia March 1996 - November 1999

Skills

UX UI DESIGN

User Research,
Competitor Analysis,
Usability Testing,
Heuristic Evaluation
Information Architecture,
Redlining & Annotations,
Wireframing,
Mockups,
Prototyping,
Interaction Design,
Mobile App Design
Responsive Web Design,
Brand Style Guides

GRAPHIC DESIGN

Brand Identity, Print & digital Design, Illustration, Brand Style Guides

Tools

Adobe CC -Photoshop, XD, Illustrator, Indesign. Figma, Miro, Trello

LANGUAGES

Basic - HTML, CSS, Javascript